I have my meat here.
Look how it's now boiling like that.
I'm going to place my meat in here and put it all together.
Mixing it all up good.
I'm going to put in here like this and mix it up.
Look at that.
Make sure that you mix it real well because the meats were separate.
If you were doing that grinding, like I said before, if you were grinding your own meat.
If you had selected your meat and grind it together, then you wouldn't have to do that.
I didn't do that.
My mom does that.
She selects her own pieces of meat and she does that.
I just buy precut, predone in the market.
I'm trying to mix all the sauce and the meat together.
All the sauce and the meat so we can have a nice amount stirring it over and over again.